

                                      THE


                  _  __      _       _     _                __ 
                 | |/ /     (_)     | |   | |              / _|
                 | ' / _ __  _  __ _| |__ | |_ ___    ___ | |_ 
                 |  < | '_ \| |/ _` | '_ \| __/ __|  / _ \|  _|
                 | . \| | | | | (_| | | | | |_\__ \ | (_) | |  
                 |_|\_\_| |_|_|\__, |_| |_|\__|___/  \___/|_|  
                                __/ |                          
                               |___/                           
  _____                              _        _____  _                       _ 
 |  __ \                            (_)      |  __ \(_)                     | |
 | |  | |_   _ _ __   __ _ _ __ ___  _  ___  | |  | |_ ___  ___ ___  _ __ __| |
 | |  | | | | | '_ \ / _` | '_ ` _ \| |/ __| | |  | | / __|/ __/ _ \| '__/ _` |
 | |__| | |_| | | | | (_| | | | | | | | (__  | |__| | \__ \ (_| (_) | | | (_| |
 |_____/ \__, |_| |_|\__,_|_| |_| |_|_|\___| |_____/|_|___/\___\___/|_|  \__,_|
          __/ |                                                                
         |___/  


                                     #0005


 Approximately twentythree hundred years ago, the great prophet Sire, the last 
 in the line of the prophets of Discord, delivered the Principia Discordia, the 
 Final Testament. Ever since the Renaissance, its believers have been subjected 
 to difficulties. From the Inquisition in Spain and Andalucia to the ethnic 
 cleansing in Bosnia and Chechnya, the Discordian people have endured colonial 
 regime and economic and military oppression. By the means of media, Discord has 
 been given a sinister image in the eye of the public opinion, this notorious 
 image is mainly due to the ignorance and misunderstanding of the media and 
 public. A word which is often heard and associated with the acts of certain 
 individuals, claiming to act in the name of Discord, is the ancient Latin 
 word: w00t. Its significance plays an extremely crucial role in the image 
 of Discord. But what does this so widely known word mean?


 w00t has a great significance in the lives of Discordians. Like any language, 
 Latin has unique words which have a particular meaning which cannot be 
 translated precisely. The best translation known for such a word is the 
 following: a cry of joy following the owning, rooting, controlling or 
 otherwise misappropriating of another's resources. 


 w00t as presented in the Principa and any of the other scriptures implies 
 the striving of spiritual good. This w00t particularly involves change in 
 one's self and mentality. It may concern the sacrifice of material property, 
 social class and even emotional comfort solely for the salvation and worship 
 of Eris ALONE. As a result, one who practises w00t will benefit greatly in 
 the Great Fnord.


EOF