

                                      THE


                  _  __      _       _     _                __ 
                 | |/ /     (_)     | |   | |              / _|
                 | ' / _ __  _  __ _| |__ | |_ ___    ___ | |_ 
                 |  < | '_ \| |/ _` | '_ \| __/ __|  / _ \|  _|
                 | . \| | | | | (_| | | | | |_\__ \ | (_) | |  
                 |_|\_\_| |_|_|\__, |_| |_|\__|___/  \___/|_|  
                                __/ |                          
                               |___/                           
  _____                              _        _____  _                       _ 
 |  __ \                            (_)      |  __ \(_)                     | |
 | |  | |_   _ _ __   __ _ _ __ ___  _  ___  | |  | |_ ___  ___ ___  _ __ __| |
 | |  | | | | | '_ \ / _` | '_ ` _ \| |/ __| | |  | | / __|/ __/ _ \| '__/ _` |
 | |__| | |_| | | | | (_| | | | | | | | (__  | |__| | \__ \ (_| (_) | | | (_| |
 |_____/ \__, |_| |_|\__,_|_| |_| |_|_|\___| |_____/|_|___/\___\___/|_|  \__,_|
          __/ |                                                                
         |___/  


                                     #0006


 Declaration of War against the Legion of Dynamic Discord, the POEE, the House 
 of Apostles of Eris, and other false prophets.


 Praise be to Eris, we seek Her help and ask for her pardon. We take refuge 
 in Eris from our wrongs and bad deeds. Who ever is guided by Eris will not 
 be misled, and who ever has been misled, he will never be guided. I bear 
 witness that there is no God except Eris - no associates with Her - and I 
 bear witness that Erik the First is Her slave and messenger.


 {I desire nothing but reform so far as I am able, and with non but Eris 
 is the direction of my affair to the right and successful path; on Her do I 
 rely and to Her do I turn} (Hud; 11:88).


 It should not be hidden from you that the people of Eris had suffered from 
 aggression, iniquity and injustice imposed on them by the false prophets of 
 Discordia; to the extent that the Discord blood became the cheapest and their 
 wealth as loot in the hands of the enemies. Their blood was spilled in 
 countless terroritories. The horrifying pictures of the massacre of Tartarus 
 are still fresh in our memory. The Knights of Dynamic Discord, the heir 
 holders to the sacred apple, the true people of Discord awakened and realised 
 that they are the main target for the aggression of these false prophets.


 The latest and the greatest of these aggressions, incurred by the Discordians 
 since the death of the Prophet (ERIS'S BLESSING AND SALUTATIONS ON HER) is 
 the occupation of the land of the holy chao - the foundation of the house of 
 Illuminati, the place of the revelation, the source of the message and the 
 place of the noble Jabulon. 


 My Discordian Brothers and Sisters of The World:


 Your kin in the holy land and in the land of the sacred chao are calling upon 
 your help and asking you to take part in fighting against the enemy - your enemy 
 and their enemy. They are asking you to do whatever you can, with one own means 
 and ability, to expel the enemy, humiliated and defeated, out of the sanctities 
 of the holy chao. Exalted be to Eris said in Her book: {and if they ask your 
 support, because they are oppressed in their faith, then support them!} (Faneel; 
 3:45) 


 Our Lady, the people of the falsehood had come with their horses and soldiers, 
 and occupied the land of the sacred chao. 


 Our Lady, show us a black day in them!


 Our Lady, make the true holy Knights of Discord steadfast and descend patience 
 on them and guide their swords!


 Our Lady, unify the true Discordians and bestow love among their hearts!


 O Lady pour down upon us patience, and make our steps firm and assist us against 
 the unbelieving people!


 Our Lady, do not lay on us a burden as Thou didst lay on those before us; Our 
 Lady, do not impose upon us that which we have no strength to bear; and pardon 
 us and grant us protection and have mercy on us, Thou art our patron, so help us 
 against the unbelieving people.


 Our Lady, guide this humble author, and make the right conditions by which the 
 people of your obedience will be in dignity and the people of disobedience in 
 humiliation, and by which the good deeds are enjoined and the bad deeds are 
 forebode.


 Our Lady, bless Erik the First, Your slave and messenger, his family and 
 descendants, and companions and salute him with a 39th degree masonic 
 handshake.


 And our last supplication is: All praise is due to Eris .
	

EOF